Hmm. Huh?
Hitomi, come look.
Hmm?
The members-only auction.
I was just looking over the list
of what they'll have on the blog.
Ooh, what'd you find?
Well, the CEO
of Kaburagi Real Estate
is an avid art collector and putting
a number of his pieces on auction.
One of them is a painting Hitomi
has been after for a long time.
What? That one?
That isn't one
I've been wanting, though.
Not that, the one next to it.
No way. Is that A Girl from One Day?
I wasn't expecting it either.
I can't believe that it's in Japan.
Rui, I absolutely have to get it.
I know, sis.
But it isn't one of the works
going up for auction.
In fact, it's currently being held
in a storage room
on the top floor
of Akitsushima Transportation.
They're known for having one of
the most rigorous security systems
in the entire country.
It's almost impossible to break into.
Doesn't make a difference.
Well, I do know one way to get in.
Huh?
First, our objective is to steal these.
Racing through the midnight streets
Jewels swaying close to my ears
A night bird vanishing
Slipped through the long nails
and high-rise towers
Sorry, but I've been lying to you
from the very start
The truth is never what meets the eye
It's always hidden in secrets
I'm tired of boring imitations
Ephemeral blooms from liars
Artificial flowers of "truth"
I'm obedient to vague temptations
But in the end, I'll take it all!
To the beat of your pulse, ready?
Magic, magic, magic
Dance to my signal
One day, all of it, get it!
Magic, magic, magic
A fantasy of secrets, tricks unseen
Un, deux, trois, jump in, baby!
Dancing all night
Back and forth
between illusion and reality
I'll bewilder you, it's a mystery
Ignite the searchlight
That becomes my spotlight
But just staring at me
Won't tell you a thing
This is my love in labyrinth
Memory Of Dad
Listen up. We're after
the three gold-leaf tenmoku tea bowls
made by Junkei Tobari.
They're in the vault
inside Kaburagi Real Estate.
I expect this should all go to plan.
Just keep an ear out
for any other instructions.
Copy.
You got it.
Welcome in.
The intake sheet is just there.
Thank you. If you could please
take a seat, ma'am.
Of course.
Taku, let's go and pick out a seat.
Taku? Taku!
Taku, where are you?
Can I help you with something?
Oh, excuse me.
I was checking in at reception,
and I realized
that Taku had gotten away from me.
Who's Taku?
My son. He's only four.
Did you see him leaving the building?
Well, ma'am, I've been posted
at the entrance,
but I can't say I've seen any kids.
That means he must be inside somewhere.
Taku! Taku, are you hiding anywhere?
Ma'am, has your child gone missing?
Yes, my little boy.
I saw a toddler just a minute ago, ma'am.
Huh?
I think he was heading
toward the admin offices.
He went that way?
Taku, can you hear me?
Ma'am, wait a moment, please!
We'll split up and search.
One step at a time, ma'am.
Nothing beats a good trip
to the sauna.
He wouldn't be outside, would he?
I haven't seen him.
So then he must be inside the building.
Huh?
He's not here either.
We've searched the entire building
except for one place.
Are you in there? He must be inside.
There's nowhere else.
Open it. I need to get in there.
That's our vault.
We can't open it without getting approval.
It's both for the business
and the CEO's own valuables as well.
We can't open it
without his permission, ma'am.
Not to mention it's difficult
to imagine he would have gotten in there.
If it's all right by you,
I'm gonna take a look.
Who are you?
I'm staff. I work
in the maintenance department.
Excuse me.
Is everything all right?
And who are you?
Detective Utsumi, at your service.
I'm off duty, but I was walking by,
and I overheard shouting.
I know that voice.
You say a child's gone missing?
Yes, we believe
he's here somewhere,
but haven't managed to find him.
Toshio's on our six.
I see, and the woman over there,
is she the child's mother?
Taku, answer me,
where are you?
Ma'am, I'm going to help you find him.
When did this all start?
Ai, we can't let him see your faces.
Start the next phase of the plan.
On it.
Uh, I got something.
I can hear a kid crying in there.
What?
Listen for yourself.
Right.
Mommy, help me! I'm scared!
I hear him.
We have to move fast. These types of safes
are designed to be airtight.
If there's someone in there,
the oxygen level is dwindling.
What?
How much oxygen is there?
It's hard to say,
but it's possible he's already at risk.
I can't believe this is happening!
Are you really not going to open it?
Detective, as we've said,
we need the CEO's permission.
But I haven't been able
to get through to him yet.
This is insane.
Say, "I've stopped hearing his voice."
I've stopped hearing his voice!
Detective, you've got to do something!
I beg you. Taku needs your help!
So that's it,
you're gonna do nothing?
The CEO wouldn't be happy with us, sir.
Is this really a time to be
concerned about how he's going to react?
The life of a child
is hanging in the balance.
Thanks for the assist, Toshio.
If something unthinkable
happens to this child,
you'll be the one who answers for that.
I, uh...
You're absolutely right.
I've got the code!
Hurry!
Sir, please hurry and open it.
My boy!
Uh, wait, ma'am! Hold on!
A fire broke out? Damn it!
Ma'am, where are you?
Damn it, what is going on?
Ma'am, are you okay?
Ma'am? Huh?
Huh?
WE HAVE CLAIMED THE THREE GOLD-PAINTED
TENMOKU TEA BOWLS MADE BY JUNKEI TOBARI
That was Cat's Eye just now?
I still can't believe
Toshio turned up yesterday.
I gotta hand it to him,
he has a sixth sense for Cat's Eye.
But he's clueless about everything else.
We couldn't have done it
without Rui.
With that super brain of hers,
she always come up with the perfect plan.
Ai, there's no such thing
as a perfect plan.
Like yesterday, sometimes you get
thrown a curveball.
Yeah, you're right.
The most important part of a heist
is being able to roll with the punches.
That and...
And what?
You can do anything
if you put your mind to it.
At the end of the day,
you've just gotta go for it.
So listen, now that we've got
the tea bowls, what's our next move?
Yeah, they aren't what we were after
in the first place.
Exactly, and that's why we're
going to return them before long.
So why did we steal them?
Look at this. It turns out
that Kaburagi Real Estate
was auctioning off
some of the president's artwork
to keep the company afloat,
including those tea bowls.
But think what would happen if they were
stolen before the auction took place?
If the company is desperate for money,
then they'd have no choice but to put
something else on the block instead.
That's the idea.
Wait a second, A Girl from One Day
will be in the auction.
Once it sells,
it'll be transported to the top bidder.
We wait for that
rather than trying to get it
out of
Akitsushima Transportation's depository,
and we're much more likely to succeed.
There you go.
As long as we have your big brain, Rui,
there's nothing in the world
we can't steal.
Yeah, it's really impressive!
What's impressive?
Toshio! We aren't open yet!
It's no big deal.
Would you loosen up?
It's just me after all.
He didn't overhear us, right?
Anyway,
what were you talking about?
Seemed like something good.
Um, we were talking about what it takes
to make a good coffee.
You were?
Yeah, you got that right.
Whenever Rui is on the old percolator,
I just know
it's gonna be a good cup of joe.
What? Ai, uh, I didn't think you drank
regular coffee, right?
Uh, I meant a latte!
Ooh, a latte?
Yes, that. She can even do
art with milk foam. Right?
Don't push it, Ai!
She can do latte art?
I would love to see that.
Indeed, weary as my heart is, I would be
much soothed by such a beverage.
One latte, please.
Do you know how?
First time for everything.
Just put your mind to it.
And here you are. One cafe latte.
Incredible! Oh, Rui,
you can do anything, can't you?
Mmm, it's nothing.
You can do anything.
Not without the internet.
You put your mind to it.
Uh-oh! I've got a meeting now.
Thanks for the coffee.
All right. Go get them, Toshio.
Yep!
This is the inventory
of art pieces recently sold at an auction.
They're all bound to be shipped
across the Pacific
to America by freighter.
Selling the pieces is the CEO
of Kaburagi Real Estate.
Given that Cat's Eye recently stole
some of his ceramic pieces,
he's requested police involvement
for security.
I mean, we haven't gotten any kind of
announcement from them, right?
Even if we haven't,
we can't let our guard down.
They don't always tell us beforehand.
Sometimes they just leave
their calling card.
That's right. Just like the other day
when you let them slip
right past you, Utsumi.
Right, you are! That was my bad!
And yet, you're the only detective
who's even managed to come that close.
Try not to disappoint me this time.
Yes, sir! I'll catch them
this time for sure. Uh...
That girl...
What is it?
I don't know. For some reason,
she seems familiar.
Yeah, that reminds me. There's something
I can't stop thinking about.
The girl in the painting looks exactly
like Hitomi did when she was a little kid.
Yeah. It was before
you were born, so you wouldn't know,
but the model for A Girl from One Day...
was me.
Huh?
That painting is one he did
especially for me.
This is where we're going
on our date today, the sweets buffet.
Oh! That looks awesome!
You've basically got a 360 degree view
of Tokyo Bay too!
I know!
Girls, we've hit a bit of a snag.
Huh?
Okay, what's the snag?
Someone bought A Girl from One Day,
but the buyer is a museum in Seattle.
Which means that it will be
shipping to America.
What?
The auction was aimed at domestic buyers,
so I never considered
that it would get sold overseas.
Okay, then why not go after
the boat and transit anyway?
Right, I thought of that and even have
the ship's loading schematics.
But here is the vessel it's going on,
and the only way to access
the pier is by this bridge.
So that is our only escape route.
If we lose that, then we're toast.
I'm sure that we can figure it out.
No, it's way too risky.
Plus, Toshio will be there.
Just think what will happen
if you get caught.
The piece will be part
of an exhibition the Seattle Museum sends
to Japan every three years.
We're going get another shot at it.
I don't care.
Hitomi, I understand what you're feeling,
but just hold out a little longer.
We are going to get it back someday.
Look at the bright side.
You're going to a sweets buffet
with Toshio.
Forget about the painting for now
and just go have some fun.
Yeah...
Hmm.
So many choices, I can't decide.
No kidding.
Are you going to eat all of that?
I've got room
in the old bread basket.
Your plate had better be clean.
By the way, did you ever do any modeling,
like maybe when you were a little kid?
Modeling? Why do you ask?
Well, I saw this painting recently,
and the girl in it
looked exactly like you.
Huh? Where did you see it?
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm not allowed to say.
It must have been another kid.
Can't say that I remember modeling.
Guess I was wrong.
Still, though, it was beautiful.
There was a certain warmth
in how it was done.
The painter's affection for her
practically jumps off the canvas.
I'm really sorry, Toshio.
Uh, what is it?
I just remembered something
I need to take care of.
Like right now?
I'll regret it if I don't.
I promise that I'm going
to make it up to you.
Uh, okay.
Hmm.
All right! These desserts
won't know what hit 'em.
Phew! All done.
Ai? I'm coming in.
Uh, come in.
What's this project of yours?
Oh, yeah.
Rui asked me to make it for her.
So what is it for?
Don't know.
Anyway, aren't you back
from your date early?
I am.
Actually, there is something
that I was hoping you could make for me.
Huh?
And I am asking
that you don't talk to Rui about it.
Okay.
AKITSUSHIMA TRANSPORTATION WAREHOUSE
Rui, I'm sorry. But three years,
that's just too long to wait.
That's everything. All secured.
Roger. Let's hit the road.
Be ready for anything out there.
AKITSUSHIMA TRANSPORTATION CONTAINER PORT
What the... What?
It's a flash grenade!
So bright! My eyes! Somebody help!
You've done it again, Ai.
These really pack a punch.
[officers and workers
yelling indistinctly]
A GIRL FROM ONE DAY
It's Cat's Eye for sure!
We're not letting her get away this time!
Block off the pier entrance!
That's the only escape route she's got!
ROAD CLOSED
Stop right there, Cat's Eye!
This all ends today!
Looks like the kitty
picked the wrong way to run!
Even with the water below,
chances are, you wouldn't walk away
from a fall this high.
Look, you've met your match.
Nice and slow, drop the painting
and come to us.
If you won't, then I'll come to you.
No! Anyone but Toshio!
You idiot! Don't do it!
Rui, Ai, I'm sorry.
I should have listened to you.
What? Damn it! She had backup?
The Cats are making their escape by boat!
Move out!
Huh?
Honestly, what were you thinking?
Thanks, Rui.
It would've been pretty bad
if we hadn't shown up, don't you think?
And you, Ai, how did you...
This is not the time.
Let's make some waves.
Hmm.
And for the cherry on top...
Make me proud, Rui.
What the hell is this?
I don't know,
but it's about to be full of bullets!
You idiot! You can't just start shooting
when we're all piled in like this!
My deadly kung fu kick
can take it down!
"WE HAVE CLAIMED
A GIRL FROM ONE DAY"
What was that, moron?
- I'm not a moron!
That was epic, bro.
We're scot-free.
The police won't be coming for us.
With that tech, Toshio and the other cops
won't get out of there too easy.
Thank you both for being there.
You really saved my butt.
Ah, you know we got you.
Although, how did you manage to find me
at the exact right moment?
It wasn't me. Our sister
was the one who put this together.
I asked you not to talk
to her about it, remember?
Oh, I didn't say anything.
You didn't?
Actually, by the time you asked me
to make some gear for you,
she had already asked me
to help with this.
Huh? Are you saying
that Rui has known the entire time
that I was going to steal this painting?
I've known you
for a good long while, you know.
I saw your face and knew
that you wouldn't give it up.
But you said the heist would be too risky.
Yes, and I was right.
But sometimes, it's worth risking it,
'cause even when it's dangerous,
it can pay off.
As we say...
Just put your mind to it.
So the saying goes.
Always one step ahead...
aren't you, Rui?
I've been expecting you.
Miss Hitomi, you're risking life and limbs
to secure this painting is hard to hear.
Nagaishi, I'm sorry
to make you worried about me.
I didn't wanna lose this painting.
I was willing to do anything.
It represents a special memory with him.
I'm truly glad that you're all right.
Please, come inside.
Stunning.
Let's get
all of them back.
Every last one of Dad's paintings
and everything from his collection too.
Somewhere in these beautiful pieces
we're bound to get a clue
that will help us find him.
The more well-known
Cat's Eye becomes,
the more likely it is
that Dad will come looking for us.
Dad, we'll find you. Just wait.
The city is a sparkling passion fruit
That winks every night
Passion beat inside the glass
I'll fall in love after one sip
lf the wind catches a sweet melody tonight
A secret door will open somewhere
Cat's Eye gazing
Shimmering green
Mysterious Cat's Eye
Basking in moonlight